Apple number 59 which probably really
don't do Glenny these things because
it's hundred of them come from rapidly
the time to research everything is a I
know I've lost it oh three day 3d
printing library so if you come for
something that's neat you can post it
there and anyone can download it and
print it themselves from there their own
3d printer and of course that makes a
lot of what any object that can be 3d
printed is then available to everyone
who has a 3d printer and with centers
that offer 3d printing to anyone such as
libraries in a lot of cities you don't
necessarily need to own a 3d printer to
be able to access the 3d library and
benefit from it so Apple number 59 is a
3d printing library